Guide to the Stanley Milgram Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Data Files, 1960-1984; Series V
  - Obedience, 1961-1963
    - Data by Condition
      - Condition 13
        - Audiorecordings of breakoffs, 2 (Box 125e–125f)
          - Transcripts, 1961 (Box 127, Folder 17)
        - Subject files, unredacted, subjects 1301-1340, 1961 (Box 120, Folder 132-171)
      - Condition 14
        - Audiorecordings of experiments, subjects 1401-1436, x1401-x1405, 4 (Box T40–T43)
        - Audiorecordings of breakoffs and interviews, 1 (Box 125f)
        - Subject files, unredacted, subjects 1401-1436, x1428, x1437-x1440, 1961-1962 (Box 121, Folder 1-41)
      - Condition 15
        - Audiorecordings of experiments, subjects 1510-1514, 1524-1530, x1501-x1503, 4 (Box T40–T41, Box T43–T44)
        - Audiorecordings of experiments[?], 1 (Box 148)
        - Audiorecordings of breakoffs and interviews, 1 (Box 125f)
          - Transcripts, 1962 (Box 127, Folder 18)
        - Subject files, unredacted, subjects 1501-1504, 1506, 1510-1530, x1501-x1505, 1961-1962 (Box 121, Folder 42-63)
      - Condition 16
        - Audiorecordings of experiments, subjects 1601-1615, x1601-x1605, 3 (Box T42, Box T45–T46)
        - Audiorecordings of breakoffs, 1 (Box 125f)
          - Transcripts, 1962 (Box 127, Folder 19)
        - Subject files, unredacted, subjects 1601-1620, 1961-9162 (Box 121, Folder 64-83)
      - Condition 17
        - Audiorecordings of experiments, subjects 1701-1717, X1702-x1705, (0012? exploratory), 2 (Box T47–T48)
        - Audiorecording of breakoffs and interviews, 2 (Box 125f–125g)
          It is unclear if 125f contains a recordings of Condition 17, 125g appears to begin with Condition 17, subject 05.
        - Subject files, unredacted, subjects 1701-1720, x1702 (Box 121, Folder 84-104)
      - Condition 18
        - Audiorecordings of experiments, subjects 1801-1839, x1801-x1805, 3 (Box T49–T51)
        - Subject files, unredacted, subjects 1801-1840, x1801-x1805, x1807, 1961-1962 (Box 121, Folder 105-150)
        - Transcripts, break off and interviews, 1962 (Box 127, Folder 20)
      - Condition 19
        - Audiorecordings of experiments, subjects 1903-1927, 3 (Box T44, Box T46, Box T52)
        - Subject files, unredacted, subjects 1901-1940, x1901, 1962 (Box 122, Folder 1-42)
      - Condition 20
        - Audiorecordings of experiments, subjects 2001-2036, x2001-x2005, 3 (Box T53–T55)
          - Preservation masters
            - Unredacted (digital), 42
            - Redacted, 42
          - Use copies (redacted)
            - Subject 2001, 1 (Box T53Uf2)
            - Subject 2002, 1 (Box T53Ug2)
            - Subject 2003, 1 (Box T53Uh2)
            - Subject 2004, 1 (Box T53Ui2)
            - Subject 2005, 1 (Box T53Uj2)
            - Subject 2006, 1 (Box T53Uk2)
            - Subject 2007, 1 (Box T53Ul2)
            - Subject 2008, 1 (Box T53Um2)
            - Subject 2009, 1 (Box T53Un2)
            - Subject 2010, 1 (Box T54Ua2)
            - Subject 2011, 1 (Box T54Ub2)
            - Subject 2012, 1 (Box T54Uc2)
            - Subject 2013, 1 (Box T54Ud2)
            - Subject 2014, 1 (Box T54Ue2)
            - Subject 2015, 1 (Box T54Uf2)
            - Subject 2016, 1 (Box T54Ug2)
            - Subject 2017, 1 (Box T54Uh2)
            - Subject 2018, 1 (Box T54Ui2)
            - Subject 2019, 1 (Box T54Uj2)
            - Subject 2020, 1 (Box T54Uk2)
            - Subject 2021, 1 (Box T54Ul2)
            - Subject 2022, 1 (Box T54Um2)
            - Subject 2023, 1 (Box T54Un2)
            - Subject 2024, 1 (Box T54Uo2)
            - Subject 2025, 1 (Box T54Up2)
            - Subject 2026, 1 (Box T54Uq2)
            - Subject 2027, 1 (Box T55Ua2)
            - Subject 2028, 1 (Box T55Ub2)
            - Subject 2029, 1 (Box T55Uc2)
            - Subject 2030, 1 (Box T55Ud2)
            - Subject 2031, 1 (Box T55Ue2)
            - Subject 2032, 1 (Box T55Uf2)
            - Subject 2033, 1 (Box T55Ug2)
            - Subject 2034, 1 (Box T55Uh2)
            - Subject 2035, 1 (Box T55Ui2)
            - Subject 2036, 1 (Box T55Uj2)
            - Subject x2001, 1 (Box T53Ua2)
            - Subject x2002, 1 (Box T53Ub2)
            - Subject x2003, 1 (Box T53Uc2)
            - Subject x2004, 1 (Box T53Ud2)
            - Subject x2005, 1 (Box T53Ue2)
        - Subject files, subjects 2001-2040, x2018, 1962 (Box 122, Folder 43-83)
          - Redacted (Box 153, Folder 1-40)
      - Condition 21
        There are no recordings for this condition in the collection.
        - Subject files (predictions of behavior, student) (Box 123, Folder 1)
        - Subject files (predictions of behavior, psychiatrists), 1963? February 1 (Box 123, Folder 2)
        - Subject files (predictions of behavior, public), 1963 May 21 (Box 123, Folder 3)
      - Condition 22
        - Audiorecordings of experiments, subjects 2201-2218, x2201-x2205 (Box T48–T49, Box T56)
          - Preservation masters
        - Subject files, unredacted, subjects 2201-2220, x2201-x2203, 1962 (Box 122, Folder 84-106)
        - Transcripts, break off and interviews, 1962 (Box 127, Folder 21)
      - Condition 23
        - Audiorecordings of experiments, subjects 2301-2335, x2301-x2305 (Box T55, Box T57–T58)
          - Preservation masters
            - Analog, subjects 2301-2306, 2309-2331, 2333-2335, x2301-x2302, x2303b-x2305b, 37 (Box T55Pk1–T55Pp1, Box T57Pa1–T57Pt1, Box T58Pa1–T58Pk1)
          - Duplicating masters, 37 (Box T55Dk1–T55Dp1, Box T57Da1–T57Dt1, Box T58Da1–T58Dk1)
          - Use copies (redacted)
            - Subject 2301
              - Analog, 1 (Box T55Up2a)
              - Digital, 1 (Box T55Up2b)
            - Subject 2302, 1 (Box T57Ua2a)
            - Subject 2303
              - Analog, 1 (Box T57Ub2a)
              - Digital, 1 (Box T57Ub2b)
            - Subject 2304
              - Analog, 1 (Box T57Uc2a)
              - Digital, 1 (Box T57Uc2b)
            - Subject 2305, 1 (Box T57Ud2a)
            - Subject 2306, 1 (Box T57Ue2a)
            - Subject 2309
              - Analog, 1 (Box T57Uf2a)
              - Digital, 1 (Box T57Uf2b)
            - Subject 2310
              - Analog, 1 (Box T57Ug2a)
              - Digital, 1 (Box T57Ug2b)
            - Subject 2311, 1 (Box T57Uh2a)
            - Subject 2312, 1 (Box T57Ui2a)
            - Subject 2313, 1 (Box T57Uj2a)
            - Subject 2314, 1 (Box T57Uk2a)
            - Subject 2315, 1 (Box T57Ul2a)
            - Subject 2316
              - Analog, 1 (Box T57Um2a)
              - Digital, 1 (Box T57Um2b)
            - Subject 2317, 1 (Box T57Un2a)
            - Subject 2318, 1 (Box T57Uo2a)
            - Subject 2319, 1 (Box T57Up2a)
            - Subject 2320, 1 (Box T57Uq2a)
            - Subject 2321
              - Analog, 1 (Box T57Ur2a)
              - Digital, 1 (Box T57Ur2b)
            - Subject 2322, 1 (Box T57Us2a)
            - Subject 2323, 1 (Box T57Ut2a)
            - Subject 2324, 1 (Box T58Ua2a)
            - Subject 2325, 1 (Box T58Ub2a)
            - Subject 2326, 1 (Box T58Uc2a)
            - Subject 2327, 1 (Box T58Ud2a)
            - Subject 2328, 1 (Box T58Ue2a)
            - Subject 2329, 1 (Box T58Uf2a)
            - Subject 2330, 1 (Box T58Ug2a)
            - Subject 2331
              - Analog, 1 (Box T58Uh2a)
              - Digital, 1 (Box T58Uh2b)
            - Subject 2333
              - Analog, 1 (Box T58Ui2a)
              - Digital, 1 (Box T58Ui2b)
            - Subject 2334
              - Analog, 1 (Box T58Uj2a)
              - Digital, 1 (Box T58Uj2b)
            - Subject 2335, 1 (Box T58Uk2a)
            - Subject x2301
              - Analog, 1 (Box T55Uk2a)
              - Digital, 1 (Box T55Uk2b)
            - Subject x2302
              - Analog, 1 (Box T55Ul2a)
              - Digital, 1 (Box T55Ul2b)
            - Subject x2303
              - Analog, 1 (Box T55Um2a)
              - Digital, 1 (Box T55Um2b)
            - Subject x2304
              - Analog, 1 (Box T55Un2a)
              - Digital, 1 (Box T55Un2b)
            - Subject x2305
              - Analog, 1 (Box T55Uo2a)
              - Digital, 1 (Box T55Uo2b)
        - Subject files, unredacted, subjects 2301b-2340b (Box 122, Folder 107-146)
          - Redacted (Box 152, Folder 1-40)
        - Transcripts, interviews, 1962 (Box 127, Folder 22)
      - Condition 24
        - Audiorecordings of experiments, subjects 2403-2419, 2421-2430, 2432-2440 (Box T59–T61)
          May be duplicates copies of original recordings.
          Label indicates that subjects 23, 31, 36 were not recorded or not transferrable.
          - Preservation masters
            - Analog, subjects 2421-2422, 2424-2430, 2432-2440, 18 (Box T60Pa1–T60Pp1, Box T61Pa1–T61Pb1)
          - Duplicating masters, 18 (Box T60Da1–T60Dp1, Box T61Da1–T61Db1)
          - Use copies (redacted)
            - Subject 2421
              - Analog, 1 (Box T60Ub2a)
              - Digital, 1 (Box T60Ub2b)
            - Subject 2422, 1 (Box T60Ua2a)
            - Subject 2424, 1 (Box T60Uc2a)
            - Subject 2425
              - Analog, 1 (Box T60Ud2a)
              - Digital, 1 (Box T60Ud2b)
            - Subject 2426, 1 (Box T60Ue2a)
            - Subject 2427, 1 (Box T60Uf2a)
            - Subject 2428, 1 (Box T60Ug2a)
            - Subject 2429
              - Analog, 1 (Box T60Uh2a)
              - Digital, 1 (Box T60Uh2b)
            - Subject 2430
              - Analog, 1 (Box T60Ui2a)
              - Digital, 1 (Box T60Ui2b)
            - Subject 2432, 1 (Box T60Uj2a)
            - Subject 2433, 1 (Box T60Uk2a)
            - Subject 2434, 1 (Box T60Ul2a)
            - Subject 2435, 1 (Box T60Un2a)
            - Subject 2436, 1 (Box T60Um2a)
            - Subject 2437
              - Analog, 1 (Box T60Uo2a)
              - Digital, 1 (Box T60Uo2b)
            - Subject 2438, 1 (Box T60Up2a)
            - Subject 2439, 1 (Box T61Ua2a)
            - Subject 2440, 1 (Box T61Ub2a)
        - Subject files
          - Subjects 2421b-2440b (Box 122, Folder 147-166)
            - Redacted, 1962 (Box 152, Folder 41-60)
          - Not coded and not included in analysis, 1962 May (Box 123, Folder 4-28)
        - Transcripts, break off and interviews, 1962 (Box 127, Folder 23)
      - Condition 25, Subject files, unredacted, subjects 2501-2515, 2500a-2500b, misc, 1962 (Box 122, Folder 167-182)
      - Bring a Friend
        - Audiorecording of experiment, [subjects unknown] (Box T58)
    - Data: uncoded or miscoded, 1962 (Box 123, Folder 29)
    - Data: mostly blank forms with no experimental data, condition 23?, 1962 (Box 123, Folder 30-34)
    - Occupational and age distributions, Undated (Box 123, Folder 35)
    - Correspondence with participants, 1961-1973 (Box 123, Folder 36)
    - Subjects: lists and notes, Undated (Box 123, Folder 37)
    - Subject cards, exploited, Undated (Box 123, Folder 38)
    - Subject interviews
      - Kahn interviews, 1962; 1 (Box 126i)
        - Transcripts (Box 127, Folder 24-25)
      - Long interviews
        - 1963 Feb 28
          - Audiorecording, 1 (Box 126a)
          - Transcript (Box 127, Folder 26)
            - Redacted (Box 155, Folder 1)
        - 1963 Mar 14
          - Audiorecording, 1 (Box 126b)
          - Transcript (Box 127, Folder 27)
            - Redacted (Box 155, Folder 2)
        - 1963 Mar 21
          - Audiorecording, 1 (Box 126c)
          - Transcript (Box 127, Folder 28)
            - Redacted (Box 155, Folder 3)
        - 1963 Mar 28
          - Audiorecording, 1 (Box 126d)
          - Transcript (Box 127, Folder 29)
            - Redacted (Box 155, Folder 4)
        - 1963 Apr 4
          - Audiorecording, 1 (Box 126e)
          - Transcript (Box 127, Folder 30)
            - Redacted (Box 155, Folder 5)
        - 1963 Apr 11
          - Audiorecording, 1 (Box 126f)
          - Transcript (Box 127, Folder 31)
            - Redacted (Box 155, Folder 6)
        - 1963 Apr 18
          - Audiorecording, 1 (Box 126g)
          - Transcript (Box 127, Folder 32)
            - Redacted (Box 155, Folder 7)
        - 1963 Apr 25
          - Audiorecording, 1 (Box 126h)
          - Transcript (Box 127, Folder 33)
            - Redacted (Box 155, Folder 8)
        - 1963 May 2 (Box 127, Folder 34)
          - Redacted (Box 155, Folder 9)
        - 1963 May 16
          - Audiorecording, 1 (Box 126j)
          - Transcript (Box 127, Folder 35)
            - Redacted (Box 155, Folder 10)
        - 1963 May 23
          - Audiorecording, 1 (Box 126k)
          - Transcript (Box 127, Folder 36)
            - Redacted (Box 155, Folder 11)
    - Tapes, original--miscellaneous and unidentified
      - Practice cries of McD [in mock experimental situation], 1 (Box 124a)
      - McDonough practice cries, 1 (Box 124b)
      - S. Miglram instructions, no-experimenter condition, 1 (Box 124c)
        "This reel conatins the instruction given to the subject in the No-Experimenter Variation."
      - Exploratory
        - Fuhrer[?] plus laughter plus x13-x16, 1 (Box 124d)
        - F_, "I will not harm this man statement" plus x17-x21..., 1 (Box 124e)
      - Unidentified conditions
        - [Experimental situation], 1 (Box 146)
        - Early experimental condition--probably 01, 1 (Box 147)
  - Promissory note, 1965 (Box 128, Folder 1)
  - Risk taking, 1967 (Box 128, Folder 2)
    The experiental data files are restricted until January 1, 2043.
  - Small world (Box 128)
    - Korte study
      - Subject recruitment response cards, 1967 (Box 129)
      - Passbooks for completed chains, 1967 (Box 129)
      - Passbooks for completed chains, 1967 (Box 130)
      - Tracers received after analysis, 1967 (Box 130)
      - Tracers for chains 130-345, 1967 (Box 131)
      - Tracers for chains 346-535, 1967 (Box 132)
      - Tracers for chains 536-729, 1967 (Box 133)
      - Correspondence with participants, 1967 (Box 134)
      - Targets, 1967 (Box 134)
      - Targets, Negro, 1967 (Box 134)
    - Nebraska study: card punching data sheets
  - TV violence
    The experiental data files are restricted until January 1, 2047.
    - CRASS I, 1970 (Box 135)
    - CRASS I, 1970 (Box 136)
    - CLOD, 1970 (Box 136)
    - CRASS II, 1970-1971 (Box 136)
    - CRASS II, 1970-1971 (Box 137)
    - FRUS, 1970-1971 (Box 137)
    - FRUS, 1970-1971 (Box 138)
    - FRUS (non-FRUS), 1971 (Box 139)
    - MOD, 1971 (Box 140)
    - BRASS (New York), 1971 (Box 141)
    - BRASS (St. Louis), 1971 (Box 141)
    - BRASS (St. Louis), 1971 (Box 142)
    - BRASS (St. Louis), 1971 (Box 143)
    - Hotel study, 1971 (Box 143)
    - Telephone study, Circa 1971 (Box 143)
    - Telephone study: audio tapes, Circa 1971 (Box 144)
  - Unidentified
    - Narration, Team 3, Undated; 1 (Box 165)
    - Shake It, Shake it, Team 3, Undated; 1 (Box 166)
    - Subject calls, Undated; 1 (Box 167)
    - [Advertising pitch], Undated; 1 (Box 168)
    - [Milgram explaining microphone use], Undated; 1 (Box 169)
    - No Exit, first and second pairs, Undated; 1 (Box 170)
    - Third No Exit ending, Undated; 1 (Box 171)
- Oversize
  - General Files
    - Alphabetical
      - Photographs of Milgram, Undated (Box 145, Folder 1)
  - Studies
    - New York-Paris
      - New York City image
        - Data analysis
          - Photographs and maps, Undated (Box 145, Folder 2)
          - Photographs and maps, undated (Folder 172, Folder 74)
      - Paris study
        - Data analysis
          - Rides and walks, Undated (Box 145, Folder 3)
          - Etude sur L'Image de Paris, 1973 August (Box 145, Folder 4)
          - Etude sur L'Image de Paris: dépouillments complimentaires, volume 1, 1973 August (Box 145, Folder 5)
    - Obedience
      - Data analysis
        - Computer printouts, Undated (Box 145, Folder 6)
        - Computer printouts, Undated (Box 145, Folder 7)
        - Computer printouts, Undated (Box 145, Folder 8)
        - Computer printouts, Undated (Box 145, Folder 9)
    - Small world
      - Data analysis: Nebraska study, 1967 (Box 145, Folder 10)
      - Data analysis: Nebraska study, 1967 (Box 145, Folder 11)
  - Writings
    - Published
      - Obedience to Authority: An Experimental View (1974)
        - Illustrations, Pre-1974 (Box 145, Folder 12)
      - Galerie Gerald Piltzer exhibit: "Paris Psychologique" (1975)
        - Negatives, Circa 1975 (Box 145, Folder 13)
        - Photographs, Circa 1975 (Box 145, Folder 14)
      - The Individual in a Social World, Essays and Experiments (1977)
        - Illustrations, Pre-1977 (Box 145, Folder 15)
    - Unpublished
      - Photography as a Human Activity
        - Manuscript, Circa 1977 (Box 145, Folder 16)
        - Reference articles volume, Circa 1977 (Box 145, Folder 17)
    - Speeches
      - Conceptual Analysis of Obedience (1968 Oct 24), 1968 October 24 (Box 145, Folder 18)
  - Teaching Files
    - City University of New York
      - Experimental social Psychology (U747)
        - "Familiar Stranger" study (at train station), 1971 Spring (Box 145, Folder 19)
        - "Telephone" study: data analysis, 1975 Spring (Box 145, Folder 20)
        - "Telephone" study: data analysis, 1975 Spring (Box 145, Folder 21)
  - Data Files
    - Small world
      - Nebraska study, Undated (Box 149)
  - Studies
    - TV Violence
      - Study conditions
        - Telephone study: TV spot, video master, 1971 January 29 (Box 150)
        - Telephone study: TV spot, video E.E. master, Circa 1971 (Box 151)
- Additional Material, 1956-1984; Accession 2008-M-029; 0.25
  - Correspondence to and from Milgram
    - 1967-1977 (Box 1, Folder 1-2)
    - 1980 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - 1981 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - 1982 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - 1983 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - 1984 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Studies
    - Memory and Learning Project letter sent to participants (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Science Beat, CBS Radio Network script, "Squares and Pegs," relating to an experiment on conformity conducted by Milgram, 1962 January 21 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Writings
    - "National Character from the Standpoint of Social Psychology", 1956 May (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - "A Psychologist Looks at Networking", undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Additional Material, Circa 1956-1984; Accession 2009-M-021
  The accession is comprised of Milgram's Harvard graduate school notebook and audio recordings of speeches, lectures, and unidentified events.
  - Harvard course notes, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 1-2)
  - Audiotapes
    - "The Answer Man, shows: 5-25-6-50 and 8-14-45", Circa 1945-1950; 1 (Box 2)
    - "Crosstalk", Undated; 1 (Box 3)
    - "Conformity", Undated; 1 (Box 4)
    - "Cyranoids," talk at APA, 1984; 1 (Box 5)
    - "Ethics Lecture", 1976 March 4; 1 (Box 6)
    - "Harper & Row, Dr. Milgram Audio-Coll", Undated; 1 (Box 7)
    - "Harry apprised of an idea, 310A" and "Antonelli, 310B", 1976 August 5; 1 (Box 8)
    - "Human Agression and Nonverbal Communication. Soundtrack", 1976 August 3; 1 (Box 9)
      Recorded at screening for Harper.
    - "Hypnosis", Undated; 1 (Box 10)
    - "The Individual & Authority" Dr. Stanley Milgram, 1977 November 21; 1 (Box 11)
    - "Mass Media Lecture #1", Undated; 1 (Box 12)
    - "Media course, Tape 1", Undated; 1 (Box 13)
    - "Media course, Tape 2", Undated; 1 (Box 14)
    - "NY-2-40", Undated; 1 (Box 15)
    - "NY Academy, Stanley Milgram TV talk", Undated; 1 (Box 16)
    - "[NY] Life, 218 A" and "218-B", May 28; 1 (Box 17)
    - "NYU Editing Workshop", Undated; 1 (Box 18)
    - Norwegian workers, recording of, Undated; 1 (Box 19)
    - "Obedience to Authority" [commercially produced], Undated; 1 (Box 20)
      Recording of show "The Literary Guild's First Edition", on in which Milgram is a guest.
    - Recording of conference on obedience to authority, 1977-10-29; 1 (Box 21)
      Labeled "[Orne] discussion: Another Time II", however the recording is of a conference on obedience to authority held at the Waldorf Astoria in NYC on Oct. 29, 1977. The conference was sponsored by the Research Foundation for Mental Hygiene and the Harlem Valley Psychiatric Center. The featured speakers were John W. Dean III, Stanley Milgram, Herbert Spiegel, and Thomas Szasz.
    - "Orne Debate", 1969 February 19; 1 (Box 22)
    - "Paris - New York Film", Undated; 1 (Box 23)
    - "Paris, French conversations", 1958; 1 (Box 24)
    - "Pat Collins CBS TV--2", 1974 February 8; 1 (Box 25)
    - "Psych Today" and "From Another Time", Undated; 1 (Box 26)
    - "The Psychological City, APA Washington, DC", Undated; 1 (Box 27)
    - "Silver #3 NY-1-50", Undated; 1 (Box 28)
    - "Social Representations I", Undated; 1 (Box 29)
    - "Social Psychology in the '80s," Milgram at N. Y. Area Social Psycologists gathering", 1980 May 3; 1 (Box 30)
    - "Stanley 338A", Undated; 1 (Box 31)
    - "Talk in Paris" and "Oxy Gene: Jean Michel Jarre", 1979 January 9; 1 (Box 32)
    - "Ten Variations on a Theme by Asch", 1969 June 5; 1 (Box 33)
    - "Today Show, Obedience: McGee, Walters, Milgram", 1974 January 15; 1 (Box 34)
    - "WOR Radio, Sherry Henry Program with Stanley Milgram", 1974 January 24; 1 (Box 35)
    - Unidentified, May 1; 1 (Box 36)
    - Unidentified, Undated; 1 (Box 37)
- Additional Material, 1950-1993; Accession 2016-M-086
  Arrangement
  Material is arranged as received from the donor.
  - CBS, "The Tenth Level" by George Bellak, Circa 1974 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Films "Invitation to Social Psychology" and "Conformity and Independence", 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Obedience to Authority, French adaptation, Maurice Chevit, 1983-1985 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Communications Project, Harvard University, booklet, unused, Circa 1967 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - "Should I pet the dog?," a child's guide to dealing with animals, Undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Tenure, The Game of Academia, proposed rules and design of boardgame, Circa 1970s (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Ribbon rewinder for typewriters (external), 1975 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Harper and Row correspondence on Obedience to Authority, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - "La Croissance de Paris" slides, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, diagrams, and notes relating to obedience study, 1971-1973 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Cyranoid research forms and notes - for Marc, Circa 1980 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Cyranoids, Circa 1980-1984 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - RAI - behavior and context, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Obedience study, 1961-1964 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Film: Conformity and Independence, script, Circa 1975 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Computer printout, social influence, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Films: Non-Verbal Communication and Human Aggression, production letters, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Addison-Wesley cover for Individual in a Social World, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Addison-Wesley, Individual in a Social World publicity and distribution, including personal list, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Addison-Wesley and Random House correspondence, 1973-1977 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - The Tenth Level agreement with CBS, 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Film people: Stitt, etc., Harper and Row files, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Certificate for screening Invitation to Social Psychology at the American Film Festival, New York City, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Sixty Munutes, Safer and Williams, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Pending, Land interview, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - American Psychological Association (APA) Toronto meeting, cyranoid paper, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - "The Familiar Stranger", 1972 July (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - "Group Pressure and Action Against a Person", 1964 August (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Harper and Row correspondence on Obedience and Authority, 1971-1980 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Permissions, Little and Brown, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Film: The City and the Self
    - General, Circa 1972 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Outline of documentary, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 3)